Sex Is Power.
Disclosure is a thriller, drama, crime film directed by Barry Levinson.
A computer specialist is sued for sexual harassment by a former lover turned boss who
initiated the act forcefully, which threatens both his career and his personal life.
Tom Sanders, played by Michael Douglas.
Meredith Johnson, played by Demi Moore.
Bob Garvin, played by Donald Sutherland.
Philip Blackburn, played by Dylan Baker.
Cindy Chang, played by Jacqueline Kim.
Catherine Alvarez, played by Roma Maffia.
Disclosure is a 1994 American psychological thriller film directed by
Barry Levinson, starring Michael Douglas and Demi Moore.
It is based on the novel by Michael Crichton, released the same year.
The cast includes Donald Sutherland, Caroline Goodall and Dennis Miller.
Douglas plays a CEO whose ex-girlfriend (Moore), an executive, files a
sexual harassment complaint after she fails to seduce him.
Disclosure was released by Warner Bros.
on December 9, 1994, received mixed reviews from critics and
grossed $214 million against its $50 million budget.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, seattle,
washington, employee, workplace, sexual harassment.
The tone is emotional and intense.